<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stocks on Connor's Investing Research</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/categories/stocks/</link><description>Recent content in Stocks on Connor's Investing Research</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 14:50:32 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/categories/stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Do I Start Investing?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/how-to-start-investing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 14:50:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/how-to-start-investing/</guid><description>What is investing? How do I start investing? What should I invest in? Is investing safe? All of these questions and more will be answered here to help you begin your investing journey
What Is Investing? There are a few ways to invest, and a couple of things you can invest. The most notable ways are investing your time and investing your money. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll be explaining how to invest your money, and making your money work for you.</description></item><item><title>How Do You Invest Under 18?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/how-to-invest-under-18/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 14:50:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/how-to-invest-under-18/</guid><description>How do you Invest as a Minor? If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever tried to sign up for a stock/crypto exchange, you&amp;rsquo;d know that they require Know Your Customer (KYC) verification. A KYC check&amp;rsquo;s purpose is to attempt to verify someone&amp;rsquo;s identity, and almost all major trading platforms/exchanges require it. You&amp;rsquo;ll be asked for things such as your SSN, driver&amp;rsquo;s license, passport, and possibly more. This makes it impossible for someone that&amp;rsquo;s under the age of 18 to create their own account.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 Stock Trading Platforms 2021</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/top-5-stock-platforms-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 19:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/top-5-stock-platforms-/</guid><description>1) Webull Webull takes the cake in my opinion as a stock trading platform. It has 0 fees, after-hours trading, a pretty simple interface, and you can even trade a selection of cryptocurrencies there. They also have a great deal to new investors that includes up to 4 free stocks, that can be valued up to $1850. Overall, a great platform that I have never had a complaint with, and that&amp;rsquo;s why it takes the number 1 spot on this list.</description></item></channel></rss>