<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Crypto on Connor's Investing Research</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/categories/crypto/</link><description>Recent content in Crypto on Connor's Investing Research</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 17:47:32 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/categories/crypto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How To Make Passive Income In Cryptocurrency</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/how-to-make-passive-income-crypto/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 17:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/how-to-make-passive-income-crypto/</guid><description>There are plenty of ways to make passive income in cryptocurrency, even more than in any traditional markets such as the stock market. Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about some ways to make passive income in crypto and how to actually do it.
How Can I Make Passive Income? Well in cryptocurrency, there are plenty of good ways to make some passive income. The top ways to make passive income that I&amp;rsquo;d recommend is staking, lending, mining, and gaming.</description></item><item><title>What is Dragonary? (Crypto Game Review)</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-dragonary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 20:17:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-dragonary/</guid><description>Dragonary is a very new and popular NFT collecting game where you can play for free, battle, train, and much more with future updates
What is Dragonary? Dragonary is an NFT collecting game where you have the choice to play for free and play to earn. You start with 3 free common dragons, and you can mine CYT with those dragons, earning a small amount per day. Once you have your 3 common dragons to at least 1/2 of their max level, you can breed them.</description></item><item><title>What is Splinterlands? (Crypto Game Review)</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-splinterlands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 17:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-splinterlands/</guid><description>Splinterlands is a card strategy game similar to Hearthstone, but with Play-to-Earn mechanics. It’s recently grown in popularity, and today we’re going to talk about what Splinterlands is, if you can make money off of it, and much more.
What is Splinterlands? Splinterlands is a strategy game that involves using cards to defeat your opponents. You can play on desktop and mobile, making it widely accessible. There are currently ranked matches, seasons, and even tournaments, giving the player a variety of things to do.</description></item><item><title>What is Crypto Gaming?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-crypto-gaming/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 16:50:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-crypto-gaming/</guid><description>Cryptocurrency gaming is a newer niche in the crypto space, and can be a great way to make some money. Today, we’ll talk about what exactly crypto gaming is, how it works, and some good games to look into.
What is Crypto Gaming? Crypto gaming is a new way for people to make money through video games. Through crypto gaming, you can earn NFTs or crypto, both of which you can sell.</description></item><item><title>What is Stellar (XLM) ?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-xlm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 16:50:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-xlm/</guid><description>Stellar calls themselves, &amp;ldquo;an open network for money&amp;rdquo;, and this network may very well be the future of transacting with any currency. Similar to XRP, they both focus on transacting money, with their high speeds and low costs, yet the visions behind both projects are very different. We&amp;rsquo;ll talk about what exactly Stellar is, the problem it&amp;rsquo;s solving, the development team behind the project, the likely future of Stellar, and even a price prediction.</description></item><item><title>How Do I Start Investing?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/how-to-start-investing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 14:50:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/how-to-start-investing/</guid><description>What is investing? How do I start investing? What should I invest in? Is investing safe? All of these questions and more will be answered here to help you begin your investing journey
What Is Investing? There are a few ways to invest, and a couple of things you can invest. The most notable ways are investing your time and investing your money. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll be explaining how to invest your money, and making your money work for you.</description></item><item><title>How Do You Invest Under 18?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/how-to-invest-under-18/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 14:50:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/how-to-invest-under-18/</guid><description>How do you Invest as a Minor? If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever tried to sign up for a stock/crypto exchange, you&amp;rsquo;d know that they require Know Your Customer (KYC) verification. A KYC check&amp;rsquo;s purpose is to attempt to verify someone&amp;rsquo;s identity, and almost all major trading platforms/exchanges require it. You&amp;rsquo;ll be asked for things such as your SSN, driver&amp;rsquo;s license, passport, and possibly more. This makes it impossible for someone that&amp;rsquo;s under the age of 18 to create their own account.</description></item><item><title>What is an NFT?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-an-nft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:30:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-an-nft/</guid><description>What is an NFT? An NFT is short for a non-fungible token, which means a digital piece that cannot be replaced, making it completely unique. An NFT can be anything from a piece of artwork to a clip of Tom Brady throwing a touchdown. You can relate an NFT to a baseball card, or some sort of other collectible item. Both examples are unique items that cannot be replaced. A common misunderstanding of NFTs is that you can simply take a screenshot of them, and then you own that NFT as well.</description></item><item><title>What is Litecoin (LTC)?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-litecoin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 01:08:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-litecoin/</guid><description>What is Litecoin? Litecoin is widely known as the silver to Bitcoin&amp;rsquo;s gold. It is a lighter version of Bitcoin, meaning that transactions are faster and cheaper. Similar to Bitcoin, it follows a Proof of Work (PoW) consensus model. This means that miners are used to mine and secure the Litecoin blockchain. It is a veteran in the cryptocurrency space and was based on Bitcoin. The goal of Litecoin is to become the real-world currency that is used to send and buy things.</description></item><item><title>What is Uniswap (UNI)?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-uniswap/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 16:30:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-uniswap/</guid><description>What is Uniswap? Uniswap is a DeFi token that is used to decentralize swapping coins. It is very similar to Pancakeswap, with the big difference being that one is built on the Binance Smart Chain, and the other is built on the Ethereum blockchain. Uniswap has been the most used decentralized exchange (DEX) for a while, do to the fact that it leads all other Ethereum DEXs.
What Problem Is It Solving?</description></item><item><title>What is Dogecoin (DOGE)?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-dogecoin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 16:24:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-dogecoin/</guid><description>What is Dogecoin? Dogecoin is a cryptocurrency that doesn&amp;rsquo;t have any functionality. Dogecoin is a fork of the Litecoin blockchain and has no utility outside of that. It follows a Proof of Work (PoW) consensus model as well as it being an inflationary coin. Overall, this is a joke of a coin that is by no means a good investment.
What Problem Is It Solving? There is no problem that Dogecoin is solving directly.</description></item><item><title>What is Polygon (MATIC)?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-matic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 15:18:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-matic/</guid><description>What is Matic? Matic is a layer-2 scaling solution for Ethereum that is meant to improve Ethereum. Matic is built upon Ethereum and is used by developers to launch their own custom blockchain that is compatible with Ethereum. The goal of Matic is a world of blockchains that are easily able to exchange information. This project was once called the Matic Network, but recently re-branded and is now known as Polygon.</description></item><item><title>What is a Smart Contract?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-are-smart-contracts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 12:56:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-are-smart-contracts/</guid><description>Smart Contracts A smart contract simply put are contracts that self execute based upon certain criteria that is coded into the smart contract. These contracts exist in a blockchain, where it is completely decentralized. When a smart contract is coded, they are written as if-then statements. For example, if the weather drops below 60 degrees, then send an alert to this person&amp;rsquo;s phone. Smart contracts are a very safe way of carrying out agreements, by use of a blockchain.</description></item><item><title>What is Ethereum (ETH)?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-ethereum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 17:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-ethereum/</guid><description>What is Ethereum? Ethereum is the largest smart contract platform in the world and has been one of the first movers in the smart contract space. Lead by Vitalik Buterin and his team of developers, Ethereum was created, which has grown to become the second-largest cryptocurrency in terms of market cap. Ethereum is currently Proof of Work (PoW), similar to Bitcoin, but will be moving to Proof of Stake (PoS), in the next 12-18 months.</description></item><item><title>What is PancakeSwap (CAKE)?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-pancakeswap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 12:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-pancakeswap/</guid><description>What is PancakeSwap? PancakeSwap is a DeFi token that is used to decentralize swapping coins. PancakeSwap is built and is the biggest DEX (Decentralized Exchange) on the Binance Smart Chain. Pancake Swap works by using Binance Smart Chain coins in your cryptocurrency wallet, and swaps that into the chosen token. You can only swap BSC tokens (Binance Smart Chain) into other tokens on the BSC. You can also stake your Pancake Swap tokens for around 120% APY.</description></item><item><title>What is Aave (AAVE)?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-aave/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 12:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-aave/</guid><description>What is Aave? Aave is a decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol that allows people to lend out as well as borrow their cryptocurrency. This allows them to avoid the centralized way of doing it, while at the same time saving more. You can either lend out crypto you already own for interest back on it, or you could borrow cryptocurrency while paying a fee. Aave is a decentralized autonomous organization (DAO), meaning that it is governed by the Aave token holders.</description></item><item><title>What is Theta (THETA)?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-theta/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 19:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-theta/</guid><description>What is Theta? Theta is a decentralized video streaming service that is built to revolutionize the video streaming space. There are two Theta tokens, there is Theta and Theta Fuel. Theta is the governance token, while Theta Fuel is what is used to power the platform.
What Problem Is It Solving? Theta is focusing on fixing a few different problems. Currently, video streaming services such as Youtube, Twitch, Hulu, and Netflix all are centralized, have some sort of fee/ad system to make them money, and poor infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>What is Polkadot (DOT)?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-polkadot/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 19:47:32 -1200</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-polkadot/</guid><description>What is Polkadot? Polkadot is a smart contract platform that is built to be interoperable. In the far future, I think similar to the current technology giants, there won&amp;rsquo;t be a single winner. This is why interoperability is so important. Blockchains must be able to work with each other, because without that ability, they will be left in the past. Polkadot already has smart contracts enabled, and is already rolling out it&amp;rsquo;s parachains.</description></item><item><title>What is Chainlink (LINK)?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-chainlink/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 19:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-chainlink/</guid><description>What is Chainlink? Chainlink is an oracle token that links the real world to the blockchain. Chainlink is used on smart contract platforms to make smart contracts more expansive in the things that can be coded into them. For example, in a sports betting scenario, the betting odds would change if one team had a large point advantage over another. This is where Chainlink comes in. Chainlink allows these contracts to use information in the outside world.</description></item><item><title>What is Vechain (VET)?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-vechain/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 19:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-vechain/</guid><description>What is Vechain? Vechain is a supply management coin that&amp;rsquo;s used by mostly businesses to revolutionize their company. Vechain is used for many different purposes, from checking if a pair of shoes aren&amp;rsquo;t fake, to the temperature of the truck your steak was transferred in. The use case for Vechain is huge, and they do have proof that this product is functional. Vechain has dozens of partnerships with some big name companies.</description></item><item><title>What is Cardano (ADA)?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-cardano/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 19:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-cardano/</guid><description>What is Cardano? Cardano is a smart contract platform that is built for the future. A smart contract platform is used to design decentralized contracts. The way this works is they are if-then contracts. For example, if the weather is above 95 degrees out, then send out a heat advisory warning. This is just one example of the many use cases of these. The biggest smart contract platform currently is Ethereum, with a current market cap of 280 billion, as well around 1.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 Cryptocurrencies to buy for 2021</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/top-5-cryptos/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 19:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/top-5-cryptos/</guid><description>1) Cardano Cardano takes the cake in my opinion as the safest way to get a high ROI. Cardano is a smart contract token that is being developed by a team led by a co-creator of Ethereum. In August of this year, the Goguen Mainnet will be released. This upgrade will enable smart contracts on the platform. Cardano already has an established ecosystem, even though we are still this far away from this upgrade.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 Crypto Exchanges 2021</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/top-5-crypto-platforms/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 19:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/top-5-crypto-platforms/</guid><description>1) Binance Depending on where you live, Binance could vary as a top rated exchange. For the people that live in the United States, you have to sign up for Binance US. For people who live outside the US, you can use the normal Binance. The difference between these two is Binance US has a much smaller selection of coins, but the tradeoff with that is it is very secure. The normal Binance is pretty much the opposite, with it having a large selection of coins, but it still quite secure.</description></item></channel></rss>