<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gaming on Connor's Investing Research</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/categories/gaming/</link><description>Recent content in Gaming on Connor's Investing Research</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 20:17:32 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/categories/gaming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is Dragonary? (Crypto Game Review)</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-dragonary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 20:17:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-dragonary/</guid><description>Dragonary is a very new and popular NFT collecting game where you can play for free, battle, train, and much more with future updates
What is Dragonary? Dragonary is an NFT collecting game where you have the choice to play for free and play to earn. You start with 3 free common dragons, and you can mine CYT with those dragons, earning a small amount per day. Once you have your 3 common dragons to at least 1/2 of their max level, you can breed them.</description></item><item><title>What is Splinterlands? (Crypto Game Review)</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-splinterlands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 17:47:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-splinterlands/</guid><description>Splinterlands is a card strategy game similar to Hearthstone, but with Play-to-Earn mechanics. It’s recently grown in popularity, and today we’re going to talk about what Splinterlands is, if you can make money off of it, and much more.
What is Splinterlands? Splinterlands is a strategy game that involves using cards to defeat your opponents. You can play on desktop and mobile, making it widely accessible. There are currently ranked matches, seasons, and even tournaments, giving the player a variety of things to do.</description></item><item><title>What is Crypto Gaming?</title><link>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-crypto-gaming/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 16:50:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kindahangry.github.io/website-investing/posts/what-is-crypto-gaming/</guid><description>Cryptocurrency gaming is a newer niche in the crypto space, and can be a great way to make some money. Today, we’ll talk about what exactly crypto gaming is, how it works, and some good games to look into.
What is Crypto Gaming? Crypto gaming is a new way for people to make money through video games. Through crypto gaming, you can earn NFTs or crypto, both of which you can sell.</description></item></channel></rss>